Okay, I don't know.
Before you start, is it okay if I record this, just because if there's any technical info
so I can remember it later?
Okay, yeah, for sure.
You don't mind?
No, I don't mind.
Okay, thank you.
I'm not recording your face, just the audio.
But you should.
Yeah, I should.
I don't know how, that's the reason why not.
Okay.
So yeah, different topic to address today.
I don't know if Gary is going to join us or if there are only the two of us.
Gary is just very rarely in these days.
He has a lot of personal things to deal with at the moment.
Okay.
Okay, I hope he's doing well.
Okay, so yeah, basically, what I want to highlight today is the status of the marketplace and
specifically the configuration of your profile and that.
So I've been looking a bit on your product and offer catalog recently.
And I think there is a different thing that we can do to enhance your visibility on that.
But I think this is also related with the technical aspect and questions you might have
on that matter.
So maybe you want to start with your questions on that?
Yeah, I mean, you've seen that I've tried lots of uploads and it only really works with
so on the development side, on the dev side, my app connects to the dev marketplace, the
dev environment, and it can upload products on.
So obviously, I haven't tried it on the prod side because I don't have access and I haven't
asked for access.
But so at the moment, we are pulling live data from our system, accurate data.
And at the moment, I'm uploading it on the prod upload as with the wizard and it works
with the wizard.
The problem is when I pull it offers, just the offers and try to upload them, I'm getting
lots of matching errors.
And what I don't understand is you have a master catalog.
So I don't understand why would it not be easier if I don't upload products and I just
And only upload the offers?
You can definitely handle things like that.
I think the pain point on your side is to ensure that you are well connected to the
product.
And for that, I think the easiest way for me to explain, let me find a template and
that I'll show you.
This one should do the trick.
The idea is to ensure that you are saying to the system, okay, I'm sending you this
information and this information is that type, that product ID type.
So I'll share my screen.
I've been trying to use MPN title.
Is that the correct?
That's the correct one.
So let's review.
Okay.
Are you seeing my screen on that?
I see.
Okay.
I think, well, there is something wrong in your upload.
It is related to those two columns.
The MPN title, I think the best way for you to really understand and to maybe with the
mapping also is to work with the template, the upload template file and that.
So there you need to provide the MPN title that you can find there.
So it is automatically created by the system, but for the hardware part, this is quite easy
because the MPN title is corresponding to the column G, the MPN one.
So want to ensure that this is well configured.
As of today, you can just say, okay, this column is called needs to be informed there.
And then you say to the system, okay, I'm sending you an offer.
This is the configuration of my offer.
That is the MPN title, not anything else, because the system can also accept the other
one, but this is the MPN title that you need to use and that.
And then, okay, that is the MPN title that you need to look after.
The offer SKU, I think that's you got it.
And that this is only for you to match with your system.
Maybe you have some specific logic and that, but these those two ones are the one that
needs to be configured well.
It will say, okay, I'm not matching with this specific product.
So this is the product and offers upload.
And so this process seems to work when I use the wizard.
But when I should have sent in all of my error, maybe I can download the errors.
We can use that time to do a world review on that.
Okay, I'll check that.
I'll check that today because I wanted to show you something else in your product.
So, okay, so let's just go to the product.
Okay, this one.
Okay, I need to go in the prod or in the vat environment.
And that's for you.
Prod.
Okay, so if I look at my.
Okay, so for you to get the error reports, you are used to that.
Okay, I'm fine.
I'm almost there now.
So let me just pass the CSV.
So if I look at the errors.
So.
Yeah.
Okay, so.
This product does not exist.
You know, if I take one product that doesn't, can I share my screen?
Yeah, for sure.
I'm also seeing that because I'm seeing other type of error message also.
Okay, well, let me share my screen.
Okay.
All right.
I don't let me.
Okay, yeah, I'm seeing your screen.
Okay.
So we do have a different type of error.
The product does not exist is related to.
You send the.
Yeah.
Okay, so.
Okay, some of them.
You put the SKU instead of the MPT title.
Yeah, that's an error.
I only just realized that now I skipped straight over to the.
To the error message rather than so it should be using MPN title for all of them.
Yeah, for all of them.
Yeah, this way why we are promoting the MPT title instead of the SKU.
It means that the SKU when it's when it is created, we cannot manage it.
So meaning that we want to delete or reject something.
And then after a while, we decide to re upload that the same MPT title will not have the same SKU.
Yeah.
For the MPT title, we can modify it and then you just need to modify your MPT title and then
you will do you will have the corresponding match.
Yeah, so that's my fault, but I think the error still applies.
So even in the area where I am using MPT title, it's saying product does not exist.
And let me just see if that product does exist.
So I'm taking the 2201 BC.
And let me search for that.
So ending 38L.
So that product does exist.
But data from this product, data sheet cannot be merged.
Product has already been accepted.
So that product does exist on the MGC Aerospace Limited and on the Master.
But it's saying product does not exist, which is you can't do that.
So it's saying product does not exist, which is false.
Yeah, that's totally false.
Okay, I'll check on the Master side.
But that's pretty strange.
And that's okay.
So, okay.
We do have this product.
It is not restricted.
So that means that you should be able to tell that.
Maybe it is related to...
Now the price is okay.
All right, so I'll check the reason why the product does not exist.
Yeah, it is being sent by the system.
The other type of error is not related to your configuration.
Probably because of the skew, right?
So I'll check.
So yes, we need to ensure that you are only using the MPN title.
For the type of error that you are getting, the product does not exist.
I will do the check.
The second type of error that I'm seeing is this product is not available for sale.
It is related to the HQPL list that we discussed previously.
And that means that we added to create some firewall for some specific references
to ensure that customers will only find and buy in the platform the authorized part,
the qualified part that they can find in the HQPL.
It means that the reference exists in the master catalog,
but we decide to restrict the sale for some specific vendor, meaning no one on that.
So this type of error is not related to your configuration.
That is a stug on one.
The third one, because I'm seeing four different types of error,
So you do have the lead time to ship field as an invalid value.
The value must be a positive integer or must not exist the limit defined by the operator.
Okay, so I'll check what is.
So you do have that on the lead time.
Okay, so the lead time to ship.
Okay, so lead time to ship is in day.
Too long, is it?
Yes, that is too long for that.
Okay, fine.
Yes, that is great.
So yeah, I think that's the because you thought that type of delay,
it should not be there for the lead time to ship, but for the procurement lead time.
Because the lead time to ship is only in days when the procurement lead time,
I think this is also more accurate type of information, you can in days, months and weeks.
This is the procurement time is for you to get the parts before sending.
So yeah, I think this error you can bypass.
And the fourth one is the product link to the new offer.
M K P S K U S.
Okay, I think that for this one, the product.
Okay, the idea that the product linked to the new offer is different from the product link to the existing offer.
I think that this is related to the fact that you made some modification in short time.
If you do some modification, and this is the type I'm thinking of, within a day,
the system will still have in memory the first one.
Okay, if you are replacing this same configuration, but yes, it will need to be with the MPN title,
the system will then accept it.
So I think you are pretty well configured on that, we're getting the small amount of error that you are getting.
Okay, so I will do the check on my own for the product does not exist because I think this is strange.
I think that maybe there are some differences in the right things, but yeah, I'll do the check on that.
And I will fix the skew thing. Sorry, I completely didn't notice that.
That's okay. You managed to do a lot on your own on that, so that's okay. You understood it pretty well.
Okay.
Sorry, the question I have though is, can't we just, sorry if it sounds like I'm being lazy,
but if we can only sell the parts that are on the...
HQPL?
Yeah, so I've put that L030 in our system and it should only quote the L030 parts, I think.
Yeah, the HQPL is the new name, that's an aggregation of the L0303, the L08.
That is the new document, but yeah, you are already aware that the L is just the older one.
Okay, so maybe I need to update it with the one you sent me. So we can only sell those parts, right?
As of today, we are...
That's fine.
The main, the only, the reasons of existence of the HQPL is to say, okay, false discopole of part number N manufacturer,
this one is qualified, the other one is not. This is all about qualification.
So as soon as we are only speaking with the MPN as of today for the hardware,
that also means that you as a seller, you are saying, okay, I'm aware of the HQPL,
sending only what is being qualified.
The things that we are, actually we are in discussion with the quality department,
we say, okay, our vendors are already respecting the HQPL with all the information, they are up to date,
we are helping them with that. And then is to say, okay, we are allowing new parts to be uploaded and selling the platform
regarding some specification. But yeah, I think the easiest way for you, I think this is not the laziest,
but the easiest way is to use the hardware master list that we are providing.
And this master list is all about the HQPL, meaning that if you are able to do the matching between the HQPL and your own system,
yeah, you would be able to say this one is allowed. And that leads us to one of them that are...
I have a question. Yeah, please.
I think the hardware master list is bigger than the HQPL though.
What is within the hardware? Because you do have more than 150,000 parts in the HQPL,
but you do not have only hardware in that. You do have also parts that are being referred as aircraft components or chemicals and so on.
But yeah, I'll send you just this afternoon, I'll send you the up-to-date hardware master list,
and this way you will be sure to be plugged into the right product page.
That leads us to the size of your product catalog compared to the size of your offers catalog,
meaning that you do have more than 12,000 parts in your product catalog, but less than 4,000 offers come together.
So that's the first delta I want to address. And the other one, check.
Check. Yeah, and you do have a bit less than 4,000 offers.
A lot of them, only nine of them are inactive, meaning that you are providing the necessary amount of information to be able to sell them in the platform.
But this is my concern, it's more about the information for the price, for the availability, the lead time and that.
And you do have only 20% of offers with a price that is not equal to zero.
We are particularly focusing on the configuration of the offers this year,
because what we want to do with the upcoming payment system in the platform, what we want to do,
we want to ensure that when a customer goes to the platform, sees what he is looking for and wants to order it,
it does not need necessarily to go through a quotation, but can directly order from you.
And for that, it needs to add a price. And if possible, it depends on the references, I do not doubt, but also the availability.
Yeah. One of the questions I have is, should I be... I mean, first, there's a couple of things.
One is, we are still working to make sure that our app, our middleware is spitting out the correct info.
On the requests I have had, it seems to be roughly correct, but you cannot test it too much because there are thousands.
But so maybe in some cases it is not giving out all of the prices that it should do.
But secondly, there are probably cases where we need to remove parts from our catalogue because they were there before.
And again, this is something probably that the app is showing that it should not be showing.
Okay. Yeah, as soon as you are uploading or you are saying to the system that you do have this product in your catalogue,
the product will remain in the master catalogue and that.
But what I want to address more specifically is that if you do, you will need to remove some parts because you are not able to source or sell them anymore.
But what is in your product catalogue that you are able to sell in the platform,
meaning that between the 12,000 parts and the 4,000 offers, where is the reality of the catalogue?
That is what I want to address.
But if there are some, we can, if this is disturbing you, we can erase the MGC from the data provider of those reference.
But we will keep them in the system.
What for is to, as I said previously, we are taking control of the data that leads, that allows us to reject some parts or to restrain the sale of some.
So, yeah, we are keeping all the information.
Yeah. This is one of our firewalls.
So, yeah, but regarding the mapping of the offer, if you are only sending the information about what you are able to sell in the platform,
I think this is all related to the offer catalogue.
So, this is what is of interest for us.
So, do you have some specific fields when you do have some doubts regarding what you are sending?
No, I just need to, I have never cleaned it.
So, the original upload was done a couple of years before I joined.
So, I think I need to remove thousands of lines.
Because I don't know, because previously it was done by Dipu.
I don't know if you've met Dipu, but I don't know what...
Yeah, we are each in his mess.
I honestly don't know what his method was to put parts there.
So, I think what I need to do is completely re-align it with what I'm doing.
So, that will probably mean removing like 8,000 lines or something.
Okay, so I think the easiest way for us to proceed and for me to help you through that
is to provide you the hardware master list.
This way you know what you do have in your catalogue that you are still able to sell.
Okay, and then after that, to focus on the offers parts.
I mean that you don't necessarily, you don't need to have the product in your catalogue
to have an offer from what is already being sold in the platform.
And this way you ensure that you can do a full wipe of your existing offers catalogue
and start on a fresh base and ensure that you are proceeding the way you want on that
and in accordance with the list.
So, I think this is the easiest way for you to go fully live and automated.
So, what would be the problem with me deleting everything and doing a fresh upload?
Would there be a problem with that?
You will not be able to do so with the product parts, but with the offers, yeah for sure.
You can set up a system, okay I'm sending you information, those are brand new,
do not take into consideration the old one, you can delete them and then just take this information.
Okay, but then we would still be left with the situation where we've got 12,000 parts in the catalogue.
With that in mind, with your new offers uploaded, we will be able to see, okay,
in my product catalogue, those ones do have an offer, those ones do not have offers.
Okay, and then on my side, I will be able to say, okay, for those products,
MGC is not a data provider anymore and they will not appear on your site.
This way you will have the reflection between products and offers.
Okay, okay. Yeah, I mean the situation is that since Deepu uploaded the first list,
we've grown, we've doubled the first year, doubled the second year,
so we're buying stock, as much stock as we can, then we're selling it, you know, it's just crazy.
Yeah, but as soon as we are up to date on that, it will be easier for you to manage the whole interface.
Another type of information that we are looking at to promote is the availability for sure,
regarding the delay, but also with the stocks on that.
That's a shame because the interface is actually being revamped as of today, as we are talking,
because I wanted to show it to you, but with the new interface, the stock will be live displayed to the customers,
meaning that this is also an argument for the customers to choose specifically your offer on that.
Are you able, through the automation, to provide to the customers the live update stock?
Yeah, that's what I'm trying to get it to do, but when you say live, you mean through API or you mean through upload?
The way you're going to proceed with the middleware, is that you're going to send the information once a day,
three times a day, in real time, I don't know, how are you planning things?
The first step, because from looking at the documentation, it looks like we have to do an upload, like so I was thinking to do it every day,
but if the API allows it, we're more than happy to have it receive requests, if that's something you're...
Yeah, it is going both ways, and that's the idea behind the automation,
is to not create new workloads on your side, but only to manage the platform through your own system, or the opposite.
I don't know, but yes, the idea is when there is a modification on one side, it is being reflected on the other.
Yeah, so once I get these synchronization issues sorted, we can do everything, you know, it's the synchronization at the moment,
that's causing the delay, you know.
Okay, and with the offers being synchronized, you'll be able to put a price on each of them?
Yeah, like as soon as... we could have it so that as soon as a price change, or every hour or something like that,
a quantity or a price change, it uploads or something.
Okay, yeah, it will only depend on your configuration.
The idea is to have as many cron jobs working as you need it.
Okay, good to know. So we are almost there, regarding your synchronization.
How can we be of some help with that integration?
If we are able to help you with that, what can we do as a operator?
Well, you're helping me work through these four errors.
So after that, it's just I need... if there's something different about the way that it will work, then I need the documentation.
But, you know, once we've got the synchronization thing sorted, I'll be... if you could give me the prod...
Access?
Yeah, and then I can, you know, do these...
I think for the API, for the synchronization, it will be on your side that you will need to do the request, but I'll check.
I'll check if I need... but you are supposed to be able to... let me check.
I can see that to you right away.
Okay.
Apply users.
It looks like you do have all the authorization.
Yes.
Edit.
Yeah, you have the ability to call the vendor API, so it is on your side only.
That you will need maybe to ask for one in your profile, user profile, but yes, you are able to do so.
So I can change it to prod?
As soon as you are ready to go, yeah.
If it is working in the Val environment, yeah, you can do it.
Well, I made a mistake on the Val environment because my products upload had a trailing character on...
Okay.
So it can't match the character, so I made a mistake on the Val environment.
But that's fixed now from the export, as you can see.
Yeah, okay, cool.
I just want to get these errors done, you know, the synchronization errors, but yeah, I need from your side to know about the matching.
The product does not exist error, you know.
I'll check that.
Yeah, that's a small amount of product, but still, yeah, I'll do the check on that.
Okay.
Other things that I want you to address, yeah, news about the marketplace.
We had the opportunity to tell you that before, but it is almost live.
It will be before summer.
We do have the payments coming on that.
That's a fact.
That's not a project anymore.
They are working on that to implement the system.
That's a good thing.
That means that we help the customers do the whole process within the marketplace and help you reach new customers on that.
So that's a good thing.
Other topics, the new revamp, I'll be sending you the information as soon as it is live.
We do have one additional topic for that.
It is coming from our export control department.
As you already know, that is a big topic, the export control.
And they are asking us to exchange with our vendors to ensure that everything that is being sold by them,
they are aware of the export control classification if there is one.
How we are proceeding, we are sending you a form, an abuse form that we are preparing to help you through that.
And then we are asking if you can say to us, is there any specific classification regarding those references?
I'll be sending you the communication right after that.
I think that you are already aware of all those type of information.
I hope it will not be too big of a job for that.
But as soon as we are good to go, as soon as we are identifying those references, we will be able to say to the export control department, OK, we are audit proof on that.
But don't you have for the HQPL, already have that information?
Yes, on that. But that means that you will need to be only selling the HQPL parts.
So I think we can work on two ways.
And that is for me to provide you with the HQPL.
This way you are sure that your references will be sold in the platform and for you to just provide us the information about classification.
This way we are good to go and to ensure that everything on the platform is being allowed to be sold.
Another thing that I wanted to show you on that is, and that matter, I'll take...
OK, let me share my screen.
So the idea behind that, because we are talking about the prices, is about a new feature that we enabled recently.
But it is... you need to know that it exists to use.
So let's say I want to add a new offer, we are only speaking about the offer, about one product that is on the platform.
OK, this one, let's pretend. I want to add an offer on that because I am able to do so.
And then I will create my offer.
And then I will see, this is not the best example on that, I will see how many vendors are already selling this product and starting with what type of price.
So this was... OK, it seems that this one is only on the quotation, but let's say for another one, this one doesn't have a price.
And then you will be able to say, OK...
Yeah, I understand.
Yeah, you understand the fact.
But that means that if you are... OK, you just want to check how is your concurrent doing on that specific reference, you will be able to do so through that here.
So that might help you for some parts.
Yeah, absolutely.
OK, yeah, that's really helpful.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to help you with a batch export and that because it will be easier for you to manage, but this is not the case as of today.
So yeah, so the export control, the payments, the new interface, the competitive pricing.
And yeah, so getting the configuration of your catalog, the pricing, we talk about that.
So yeah, please.
I have seen more activity... excuse me.
Sorry. I have seen more activity since we've been uploading more products and offers in the last month, I think, month, two months, six weeks.
We definitely have had more requests.
But that's a good thing. As soon as you are updating your catalog, you are answering to the customers, this will create a type of relation with the customers.
Also, a new thing on that is that we are progressively displaying the offers to new sales organizations and M.G.C. offers are now being displayed to the UK.
Excellent.
So before that, it was only about France and Germany, sales organization.
So that's wider, that only customers because customer center can also see them.
But now what we are calling the pure marketplace, the external customers are not able to see.
OK, fantastic.
So yeah, we're working on that.
And I'm more than confident that with the payment and the communication that we're going to do worldwide to our customers, this will also help.
So this is why we need to ensure that you are up to date regarding the information that you are providing, everything that you are able to provide to the customers.
And this way, you will see the difference.
Cool. OK. That's good.
And how has this year been so far in terms of volume?
In terms of volume, I can share you those numbers from the end of March.
Presenting to me, OK.
So we are selling different categories of products, but the main ones are and remain the chemicals.
The hardware that is constantly growing on that.
So on the left side is about the number of orders and on the right side is about the value.
So yeah, the hardware is expanding and the tooling is representing a less amount of order.
But still, regarding the value, those are more expensive than Fasteners.
So yeah, we then made more than 3.3 million as of today and we've more than 2,000 orders on that.
So yeah, we are actually and more and more new customers are coming to the platform.
Sorry, which period is this?
Only for the first quarter.
For the first quarter, OK.
So for reference, last year all the categories are representing almost 13 million of GMV.
So yeah, and especially for the, as I said, the hardware category is the one that will benefit the most from the payment
because it will allow the customers to directly order with no quotation.
So yeah, we need to be sure to be ready and that is for Summer.
So for the total value of sales of hardware in the first quarter, it's about 20,000 euros?
No, more than that.
So it's 0.7%.
So wait there, is my calculations wrong?
I do have the up-to-date, for today, for the category.
30,000.
That's it.
OK, so yeah, for sure.
Last year we made more than, I think it was 120,000 euros of hardware with no payment system.
So we will see the difference.
And that means that you will be able to display your offer to a wider number of users.
Excellent.
So OK, to sum it up, I'll send you the up-to-date hardware master list.
I'll check the product doesn't exist error on my side.
And after that, if you can send me the export control form field,
and we will be good to go and to update your category.
OK, so you need me to add that as a field or you're sending me something?
I'm sending you also the form for that.
OK.
OK, maybe you do have other questions on that?
No, I'm surprised.
Thank you so much for going into the detail of the errors that I was surprised.
So I really appreciate that.
Thank you.
As I said, you manage a lot on your own.
Thank you for your work.
I'm sorry it's taking so long, but it's lots of things to do.
But I think we're almost there.
I'm pretty confident too.
I think as soon as we solve those remaining errors,
you will be good to go to the product environment.
Yeah, exactly.
OK, perfect then.
And did you have a good Easter?
Bonpac?
We are all waiting for the month of May to come,
for that to have a real sense of holiday,
because as you do know, in France in May we are practically not working.
Yeah.
Considering all the days.
It means that really for each year, for the first of January,
you do have some articles in the press saying, OK, if you are on vacation,
those days in May you will have that amount of free days.
So yeah, we are all the way in it.
Oh, nice.
I hope you have a good one.
Yeah, I do hope so.
But it's a bit of work too.
OK.
That's all from me.
And from me too for today.
So let me send you the information via mail today, this afternoon.
We'll continue this way.
Merci.
Have a great day.
Bonne journée.